

Jeremy Luscombe_

Digital Marketer

Profile

Digital marketer with a proven track-record of optimising websites for search engines, driving organic traffic, increasing SERP rankings, CRO and strengthening and diversifying website backlink profiles. Strong experience using Wordpress (5+ years), as well as experience in custom theme development. Good knowledge of HTML5, CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap, PHP for Wordpress, Javascript and jQuery.

Adept with Google Ads: increasing account KPIs, optimising campaigns through A/B testing, conversion tracking and landing page optimisation.

Details

DOB:

17/08/1989

Address:

London, United Kingdom

Phone:

07860629798

Email:

jeremy@jeremyjl.com

Website:

https://dev.jeremyjl.com

Job Experience

♦ LOGMYCARE

MAY 2020 - PRESENT | SENIOR DIGITAL EXECUTIVE

- Reporting directly to CTO. Responsible for running SEM and email marketing campaigns. Development and maintenance, including CRO and technical SEO, of flagship website.
- Direct line manager for junior marketing team members, acting as lead on collaborative outbound marketing campaigns. Responsible for personal development and upskilling of members of team.

RESONICS

2014 - 2020 | DIGITAL MARKETING MANAGER

- Head of digital marketing at London interior acoustics firm, responsible for maintenance & development of two company websites (Wordpress), running SEO, PPC, SEM & email campaigns.
- 5 x increase in organic traffic during tenure (2014: 4,000 organic sessions / month to 20,000 organic sessions in late 2019). #1 SERP ranking for numerous target keywords (e.g. "acoustic baffles").
- Sole manager of Google Ads account (£200k + annual spend). Enacted granular (SKAG) approach to Ad Campaigns, A/B testing and landing page optimisation to drive conversion rates.
- Created and disseminated blog content to increase and diversify backlink profile. 40 x backlink increase, including from high DR websites such as Bloomberg, New Statesman and Lifehack.

SR7 / KPMG

2012 - 2014 | SOCIAL MEDIA ANALYST

- Social media analyst for Sydney social media analyst firm SR7 (now integrated with KPMG), responsible for monitoring and reporting on social media risk and strategy for Australian banks and non-profit organisations.
- Outward facing consultant, providing expert advice and actionable intelligence to clients regarding their digital media strategy.
- Responsible for the production of well written, insightful risk reports for clients on a daily, weekly and monthly basis

NEWS.COM.AU

2011 - 2012 | WEBSITE MANAGER, JOURNALIST

- Production of well written, soundly researched journalistic news stories and content aimed at target demographics and audiences. Articles published on website and Sydney newspaper 'MX'.
- On-page SEO of submitted articles. Ensuring optimal heading structure, inclusion of meta tags tags and optimisation and compression of multimedia.
- Daily maintenance of website including using Google Search Console to identify indexing and crawl errors and 404s. Responsible for adding 301 and 302 redirects.

Tools

Wordpress Photoshop Google Analytics Ahrefs Shopify Google Tag Manager Google Ads Screaming Frog SEMRush Adobe XD Google Search Console

Education

UNIVERSITY OF NEW SOUTH WALES (UNSW)

2008 - 2012

Bachelor of Media & Communications, Journalism (Distinction)

SYDNEY BOYS HIGH SCHOOL, SYDNEY, AUSTRALIA

2002 - 2007

Secondary Education